Just hold your leg like this, right here.
ちょっと足をね、こう持ってて、ここ
Come on, come on, let's pull it out.
さあさあさあ、抜きますよ
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
はい、お疲れ様でした
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Yes, that's it.
はい、ということで終わりました
I'd like to take a bonus video.
特典というか、おまけ映像撮りたいんですよ
Cleaning room.
お掃除部屋
Do you understand?
分かります?
This camp I just went to.
この行ったばっかしの、この陣地
I want you to commemorate it a little.
ちょっと記念してほしいんですよ
Can you do it?
できるかな?
As usual, it's about time.
例のようにね、そろそろ
Just try it again.
ちょっとまたやってごらん
Would you use it if you reversed your hair?
髪の毛逆にしてくれると使うかな?
Yeah, yeah, oh yeah, right here.
そうそうそう、あ、そうね、こっちね
Yeah, yeah, this one is better.
そうそうそう、こっちの方がいいよ
Yes, first of all, to commemorate the urethra.
そう、まず尿道記念して
Ah, it feels good.
あー気持ちいい
あー 気持ちいい
Try sucking my urethra once.
一回ね、尿道吸ってごらん
Yes, there are some left.
そう、残ってるね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
And this cylinder, around the cut neck.
そしてこの気筒のね、刈り首のあたりね
Yes, please commemorate it.
そう、記念してください
Ah yes.
あーそう
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
はい、お疲れ様でした
Come on, oh.
さあ、お
It doesn't look dirty, does it?
別に見て汚れてるじゃないですか、
this.
これ
Please commemorate this next time.
今度、さおをね、記念してください
A pole.
さおを
What do you think?
どうですか?
Are you interested?
気になりました?
I was curious, so yes.
気になりましたから、はい
Yes, have you ever done a cleaning fella?
はい、お掃除フェラーは、お掃除フェラーはやったことあるの
Right?
よね?
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうあるのね
yes.
はい
Have you ever had a creampie?
中出しもやったことあるの?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, then there was no problem.
あ、じゃあ問題なかったですね
Yes, right.
はい、ね
Since I'm the third person, I thought I wasn't doing anything.
俺は3人目だから何もやってないのかと思ってね
I was a little surprised.
ちょっとびっくりしたんですけどね
Yes, right.
はい、ね
Yes, see you then.
はい、じゃあね
Well, please make this a bonus video.
えー、これをね、おまけ映像にしてね
I would like to.
したいと思いますよ
Okay, see you then.
はい、じゃあね、ということでね
Well, let's make this the last one.
えー、これ本当最後にしましょうね
Yes, wait a minute.
はい、ちょっと待ってね
I'll try it.
ひいてみますね
Yes, by extension.
はい、ひいて
Yes, that's good.
はい、いいですね
You can see the foreground.
前景映りましたね
Yes, right.
はい、ね
Well then, let's say goodbye.
じゃあね、これでバイバイしましょうね
Yes, bye bye.
はい、バイバーイ
See you soon.
またねー
Yes.
はーい